# Dalvan Carvalho

# **Front-End Developer**

IT specialist with over 10 years of experience in the technology field looking to leverage research and problem-solving skills in front-end development. Values collaboration with teams that share knowledge and ideas in the fields of development, design, and user experience.

#### Contact

contact@dalvanc.com

+5592 98551-8435

in linkedin.com/in/dalvancarvalho

github.com/dalvancarvalho

dalvanc.com

RS, Brazil (UTC -03:00)

#### **Skills**

#### **Programming languages**

HTML

CSS

Sass

JavaScript

TypeScript

#### Libraries and frameworks

React

Next.js

Tailwind CSS

**GSAP** 

Framer Motion

Chart.js

## Tools, platforms and others

Git

GitHub

PostgreSQL

Vercel

Figma

### **Professional experience**

## **Front-End Developer**

08/2022 - Present



- Manages **dalvanc.com**, sharing his journey in the field of front-end development and providing details about the projects undertaken, including the technologies employed in each.
- Develops responsive websites and applications (compatible with mobile devices) using modern CSS frameworks and JavaScript libraries like Tailwind CSS and React.
- Stays updated with the latest trends and technologies in front-end development, following best practices and prioritizing the maintainability and scalability of applications.

#### Coordinator

Topocart  $\cdot$  07/2019 — 08/2022  $\cdot$  Manaus, AM



- Effectively led office teams in Manaus and Brasília (the latter remotely) for the successful
  execution of tasks in projects across different locations in the country, contributing to
  operational efficiency and goal achievement.
- Used Jenkins to automate repetitive tasks, ensuring that the team always had up-to-date material to perform analyses, improving process efficiency and result accuracy.
- Ensured stability and efficiency of the IT infrastructure in the Manaus office by leading the management and maintenance of workstations, servers, and storage in close collaboration with the company's IT team at the headquarters in Brasília.

## Quality Assurance Analyst · 05/2017 - 07/2019 · Santa Cruz do Sul, RS

- Produced comprehensive reports highlighting the results of the data collected and processed during the Mapa da Cidade project, providing a clear overview of the progress and insights gained from 2017 to 2019.
- Utilized tools such as PostgreSQL to manage and process the data collected throughout the project, creating queries that simplified analysis and accelerated comparison with the database provided by the client.
- Facilitated efficient communication between the company and the client, actively participating
  in weekly alignment meetings, ensuring a harmonious collaboration aligned with the project
  objectives.

#### **IT Technician**

IDB Informática · 01/2012 — 05/2017



- Led the technical support department for over 5 years, excelling in providing remote and onsite technical support to end users. Additionally, trained new technicians and implemented methods for detecting and resolving issues at both software and hardware levels.
- Performed on-site maintenance and management of IT and network infrastructure for corporate clients, significantly optimizing issue resolution. Ensured personalized assistance, precisely aligned with the individual needs of each case, resulting in more efficient infrastructure management and lasting customer satisfaction.

## Education

# Bachelor's in Civil Engineering

Universidade de Santa Cruz do Sul - UNISC 2012 — 2018

l

SQL and Database

· The Creative JavaScript Course

• The Creative React Course

# Languages

Portuguese

Native

**English**Full Professional Proficiency

#### Interests

Tech

Design

• Urbanism

Music

Photography

Sports